discoverorg.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy

Revised May 7, 2018

DiscoverOrg is the world’s premier provider of business-to-business data for sales, marketing, and recruiting. This privacy policy (the “Policy”) describes how DiscoverOrg handles personal information collected, received, or maintained by DiscoverOrg (1) as a result of visits to DiscoverOrg’s website, (2) in respect of its relationships with customers, and (3) comprising business contact information that is part of DiscoverOrg’s products or services.

## 1\. Definitions

“Business Contact Information” means any of the following information as used in connection with an individual’s business or profession: name, title, company, business email address, business phone number, work address, public professional profile address, and/or supplementary information such as business role and responsibility designations.

“DiscoverOrg” for purposes of this Privacy Policy includes DiscoverOrg, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company, and its affiliates, including DiscoverOrg, Inc. (f/k/a Rain King Software, Inc.).

“DiscoverOrg Technology” means DiscoverOrg’s password-protected online graphical user interfaces (including those available at go.discoverydb.com and app.rainkingonline.com), DiscoverOrg’s application programmer interfaces (“APIs”), and any other software that connects DiscoverOrg’s database(s) with any customer relationship manager (“CRM”), marketing automation tool (“MAT”), sales enablement software, or other similar software, including but not limited to DiscoverOrg’s Salesforce Native Application (“SFNA”), Google Chrome Extension (“GCE”), and Marketo Webhooks (collectively, the “Integrations”).

“Services” means licensed access to DiscoverOrg’s proprietary database, which is provided via the DiscoverOrg Technology.

“Website” means discoverorg.com.

## 2\. DiscoverOrg Website

This Policy applies to the Website. It does not apply to any website of any third party, even if the third-party website links to (or is linked from) the Website. By accessing, using, and/or submitting information through the Website, you consent to the practices described in this Policy with regard to the information collected thereby as described herein. If you do not agree with this Policy, you must delete all cookies from your browser cache after visiting the Website and refrain from visiting or using the Website.

### Website Visitor Information Collected

To browse the Website only, you are not required to provide any personal information. However, we may gather non-personally-identifiable information. Similar to many commercial websites, we utilize “cookies” and other technologies to collect non-personally-identifiable information on visitors to the Website. Cookies allow web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. Cookies store information accessed through your browser to streamline activities on related web sites, and make the online experience easier and more personalized. Information gathered through cookies and web-server log files may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, IP addresses, links to/from any page, and time spent at a site.

The Website may include options for visitors to submit information to DiscoverOrg, for example, to request a product demonstration, download an article, etc. Such forms may provide the option of submitting personal information, such as your name, job title, company, email address, or phone number. In addition, when submitting information on a Website, your submission will be associated with the IP address you are then using, which is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider.

### Use of Website Visitor Information

We use cookie data to measure site traffic and usage activity for purposes of improving and enhancing the functionality of the Website, to look for possible fraudulent activity, to better understand the sources of traffic and transactions on the Website, and/or to serve targeted advertisements. Cookies also allow our servers to remember your account information for future visits and to provide personalized and streamlined information across related pages on the Website. You can choose to disable cookies for the Website but this may substantially limit your ability to use our Website. The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, or service providers is not covered by this Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

Information collected from Website submissions will be used for DiscoverOrg’s internal business purposes, including its investigations, sales, and marketing. We may use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the Services. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP address.

DiscoverOrg takes reasonable steps to maintain the security of Website visitor information, does not license or sell such information to anyone, and will only share such information with a third party who has agreed to keep such information confidential and maintain the security thereof, and only for the purposes of facilitating one of the uses described herein on behalf of DiscoverOrg.

If you have visited any of the Website and would like to know what information, if any, DiscoverOrg has about you and would like to correct such information or have it deleted, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## 3\. DiscoverOrg Customers

### Customer Information Collected

DiscoverOrg may collect the following information from or regarding its customers: (1) personal contact information regarding users of the Services (“User Information”); (2) information uploaded to our system by a user of the Services (“Uploaded Information”); and (3) usage logs regarding the use of the Services, including logins and other actions taken, time stamps, IP address, and other usage data (“Usage Logs”) (collectively, “Customer Information”). In addition, in connection with purchasing the Services, DiscoverOrg may receive credit card or other payment information (“Payment Information”).

You may be a user that has been provided access to the DiscoverOrg site and database through your company license agreement. Your employer may require that one or more users have global rights to access any and all information of every user that has access through the company. If you have questions or concerns regarding the rights of other individuals in your company to access your User Information, Uploaded Information, or Usage Logs, you should raise those concerns with the appropriate person at your company. ****

### Use of Customer Information

Customer Information may be used for DiscoverOrg’s legitimate business interests in connection with your use of the Services, including to respond to user inquiries and fulfill user requests, complete transactions, provide customer service, send administrative information, and to personalize user experience with the Services. We may use Customer Information to better understand our users in general and to improve the content and functionality of the Services. We may use Customer Information to contact you in the future to tell you about services, promotions, opportunities, and other general information about DiscoverOrg we believe will be of interest to you. We may use Customer Information to investigate and prosecute potential breaches of DiscoverOrg’s security or license agreements.

DiscoverOrg will not disclose Customer Information to any third party except in connection with a legitimate use as set forth herein, in connection with a bona fide legal dispute to which such information is relevant, in response to valid, compulsory legal process, or as otherwise required by law. DiscoverOrg will, whenever possible, obtain confidentiality agreements from any person or entity to whom Customer Information is disclosed and ensure any recipients are committed to employing appropriate technological security measures.

DiscoverOrg employs reasonable security and back-up procedures to protect Customer Information. However, in the unlikely event there is a loss or corruption of Customer Information, DiscoverOrg is not responsible or liable for such loss or corruption. We encourage our users to retain copies of all Uploaded Information on their own system.

DiscoverOrg will use Payment Information solely for the purpose of fulfilling purchase requests. We will store Payment Information in an encrypted form and will not sell, share, or use it again without prior consent.

### Customer Use of DiscoverOrg Integrations

As part of the Services, DiscoverOrg may make available to its Customers certain Integrations. In using DiscoverOrg’s Integrations, such as DiscoverOrg’s SFNA and web browser extensions, Business Contact Information from Customer’s CRM, MAT, or sales enablement software may be transmitted to DiscoverOrg for purposes of matching or cleansing Customer’s data against DiscoverOrg’s database as a feature of the Services. In that event, DiscoverOrg may retain and store such Business Contact Information for purposes of identifying potential contacts to supplement the Services, verifying the accuracy of such Business Contact Information, removing out-of-date Business Contact Information from the Services, or otherwise improving DiscoverOrg’s research processes and the content provided through the Services. Information so received will be completely anonymous as to the source. In the event that any customer wishes to opt out of DiscoverOrg’s use of such information, they may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## 4\. DiscoverOrg Services

### Information Collection and Use

DiscoverOrg collects information regarding companies and their employees, including Business Contact Information on company executives, decision makers, and other employees. The information collected is similar to that which is typically included on a business card, business email signature block, or an online professional profile, including: name, company name, job title, business email address, business phone number, business address, and corporate website URL. DiscoverOrg gathers, verifies, and organizes this data for purposes of licensing such information to DiscoverOrg’s clients and strategic partners for sales, marketing, and recruiting purposes.

DiscoverOrg obtains data for its database from first-hand research, including telephone interviews and publicly available resources, third-party licensors, and customer contributions/feedback. All of the business contact information that DiscoverOrg obtains through any of the foregoing means is verified by DiscoverOrg’s in-house research team, and information that is found to be inaccurate or irrelevant to the purposes of the Services is removed and deleted. DiscoverOrg endeavors to publish only accurate business contact information on executives and other agents and employees of the companies it profiles.

### Disclosure of Information via the Services

If DiscoverOrg has included your business contact information in its database, such information may be disclosed to DiscoverOrg’s clients and strategic partners who have entered into license agreements with DiscoverOrg. Such agreements require any such licensee to use such information only for such licensee’s internal business purposes, including sales, marketing or recruiting, and not to disclose such information to third parties. Such agreements prohibit such licensees from using any of the information in violation of any applicable law, which include laws regarding unsolicited marketing.

### EU Residents

In the course of obtaining data to be included in DiscoverOrg’s services, if DiscoverOrg obtains business contact information regarding an individual that DiscoverOrg has reason to believe is based in the European Union, DiscoverOrg will provide such individual with a notice detailing the information DiscoverOrg has on such person, the purpose for which it will be used, and informing such person of their rights with respect to such information, including the right to know what information DiscoverOrg possesses on them, to correct such information, or to opt out of data collection entirely. Such persons may opt out of the DiscoverOrg database by emailing [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## 5\. Miscellaneous Provisions

### Privacy Shield

DiscoverOrg complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. DiscoverOrg has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program (including the Privacy Shield Principles), any rights you may have to binding arbitration before a Privacy Shield Panel, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov.

For information received under the Privacy Shield, DiscoverOrg will require third parties to whom DiscoverOrg discloses personal information to safeguard that personal information consistent with this Policy by contract, obligating those third parties to provide at least the same level of protection as is required by the Privacy Shield Principles. EU and Swiss citizens may choose to opt-out of such disclosures. DiscoverOrg may have liability to you in case of failure to comply with the law or this policy in handling onward transfer of your information to third parties.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, DiscoverOrg commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Policy should first contact DiscoverOrg at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) European Union and Swiss individuals have the right to access their personal data.

DiscoverOrg further has committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to JAMS (Judicial Arbitration & Mediation Services), an independent alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and recognized for this purpose by the US Department of Commerce. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for more information, and to file a complaint.

The Federal Trade Commission has enforcement authority regarding DiscoverOrg’s compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles.

**The General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) 2016/679**

DiscoverOrg endeavors to comply with the provisions of the GDPR as to any information in its possession regarding European Union-based persons (“data subjects”). As such, DiscoverOrg only processes personal information on data subjects where it has a lawful basis to do so, which may include the consent of the person (especially in the case of website visitors who provide their information), performance of a contract, compliance with a legal obligation, or the legitimate interest of the controller or a third party. DiscoverOrg provides notice to all data subjects as required by GDPR Article 13 or 14, as appropriate, and honors the rights of data subjects provided in Articles 12-23, including the right to be forgotten. For any opt-out requests or other inquiries related to privacy, please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#017173687760627841656872626e7764736e73662f626e6c).

### Security

DiscoverOrg employs reasonable security controls to protect all of the information subject to this Policy.

### Change in Control

In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar events, any information in our possession may be transferred to our successor or assign.

### Changes and Notifications

This Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. DiscoverOrg may make updates and changes to this Policy by posting an updated policy on the Website.

### Access to Information; Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices, or use of the Website or Services, or would like to make any request as provided hereunder, please contact us at:

DiscoverOrg

Attn: Privacy

805 Broadway, Suite 900

Vancouver, WA 98660

360-718-5630

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c1b1b3a8b7a0a2b881a5a8b2a2aeb7a4b3aeb3a6efa2aeac).
